If you hear them coming, you're already dead.
Static is a drama, horror, thriller film directed by Todd Levin.
A couple facing marital problems after losing their child finds their
life together further complicated by a mysterious visitor.
Jonathan Dade, played by Milo Ventimiglia.
Addie Dade, played by Sarah Shahi.
Greg Wagner, played by William Mapother.
Rachel, played by Sara Paxton.
Head Intruder, played by Dominic Bogart.
Thomas Dade, played by Oz Kalvan.
Static is a 2012 horror film directed by Todd Levin and
starring Sara Paxton and Milo Ventimiglia.
The film explores themes of husband wife
relationship, home invasion, loss of child.
The tone is dark and mind_bending and emotional.